JAMES E. (JED) DAVIS

Austin, Texas 78745 2 469.358.5333 | jed.davis.email@gmail.com

QUALIFICATIONS PROFILE

A highly analytical, innovative, and well-organized professional with proven expert in interpersonal communication and exceptional at dealing with clients and customers. Equipped with broad experience in the coordination and implementation of on-air and online content, as well as advertising for multiple radio station websites.

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE

Adobe Photoshop | Fireworks | Salesforce | HTML 5 | CSS | JavaScript | jQuery | PHP | Laravel | SQL | Backbone | SEO/SEM | Targeted **Display Advertising**

EDUCATION

Austin Coding Academy, Austin, TX

Full Stack Web Developer 2016

PROJECTS

www.bodizypha.com www.github.com/bodizypha www.foodtruckfinderaustin.com

- During my three semesters at Austin Coding Academy I wrote code for websites, wrote scripts and built databases for class projects. Untilizing HTML5, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, PHP, Laravel, Backbone and MySQL. Some can be seen through my github listed above.
- In my current role at iHeart Media, I assist in the design of artwork with the implementation to our station websites and weekly emails for clients. This includes embedding artwork with hyperlinks, coding the dynamic leads and placing art in positions for sales inventory. Also synced interactive banners with streaming commercials within the iHeart Radio App.
- I'm currently working on a personal website application for a food truck finder in the Austin market, and will be expanding to Dallas/Ft.Worth, Houston and San Antonio. This will be downloadable summer 2016.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

iHeartMedia - Austin

Integrated Brand Manager

2013 - Present

- Partnered with station marketing managers, on-air talent, and the entire market team in to deliver the best on-air and digital consumer experience. Including copy writing for on-air/streaming, Banner Ads, Companion Ads and Targeted Display.
- · Worked in conjunction with the digital department to propose, close, and implement station specific advertising and promotional contracts with local, state, and national clients.
- Ensured on-air promotions, contests, events, and activities were synced with web components and social media.
- Coordinated sales and digital activations for key community and station events such as, but not limited to: SXSW, Country Music Live Series, and Texas Tailgate Zone.

Cox Media Group - Austin

Multimedia Advertising Consultant

2012 - 2013

- Sold advertising and event marketing to specific territory in East Austin.
- Presented Social Media Marketing, SEO/SEM and Targeted Display for Web.
- Kept daily log of contact, presentations and renewals in Salesforce.

DealerTrack Inc - Dallas

Sales Manager

Sold a Java based managed chat service to car dealership in central United States.

2011 - 2012

- Assist web development team with implementation of software to dealer website.
- Keep daily log of contact, presentation and renewals in Saleforce.